<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aaron Lee</title>
    <link>//www.aaronklee.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aaron Lee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//www.aaronklee.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reading recommendations</title>
      <link>//www.aaronklee.com/reading/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.aaronklee.com/reading/reading/</guid>
      <description>A Psalm for the Wild-Built (Becky Chambers) A Prayer for the Crown-Shy (Becky Chambers) The Master and Margarita (Mikhail Bulgakov) The Amazing Maurice and his Educated Rodents (Terry Pratchett) The Wee Free Men (Terry Pratchett) (Literally anything by Terry Pratchett) Narcissus and Goldmund (Hermann Hesse) Animal Farm (George Orwell) Howl&amp;rsquo;s Moving Castle / Castle in the Air / House of Many Ways (Diana Wynne Jones) The Earthsea Cycle (Ursula K.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warwick iGEM 2024: moving metal with bacteria</title>
      <link>//www.aaronklee.com/posts/igem/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 17:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.aaronklee.com/posts/igem/</guid>
      <description>From February to October 2024, I competed in the international Genetically Engineered Machines (iGEM) competition, where competitors developed engineered biological solutions for a variety of problem spaces.
I was a member of the 2024 University of Warwick team, BEACON, working together to engineer bacteria with the abilities to scavenge for rare earth metals, then to transport them to a singular point for collection to be recycled. We were one of 210 teams to be awarded a gold medal at the Paris Jamboree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//www.aaronklee.com/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 12:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.aaronklee.com/about/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, my name is Aaron; I am an incoming PKPD industrial placement student at AstraZeneca, and a student at the University of Warwick. I study a combination of computer science, biomedical and systems engineering, and molecular and systems biology.
My main interests lie in synthetic/engineering biology, in the application of computational and engineering methods to biomedical and clinical sciences.
Engineering biology is a field I have been passionate about since very early on in my life—I was first exposed to genetic engineering in year 8 (2018), with the release of Justin Atkin&amp;rsquo;s presentation of his DIY lactose intolerance gene therapy, and subsequent spider silk-producing yeast.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
